We have the burger builder project and there are some things we'll adjust in this module. We need to
Mamy projekt budowniczego burgerw i s pewne rzeczy, ktre dostosujemy w tym module. Musimy doda nowy widok, rejestracj i
add a new view, the sign up and sign in view, I'll combine it in one view where we can create new users or
logowanie. Pocz go w jednym widoku, w ktrym bdziemy mogli tworzy nowych uytkownikw
log users in.
lub logowa uytkownikw.
We also want to protect some routes on the frontend, guard them so that for example we can't access
Chcemy rwnie zabezpieczy niektre trasy na interfejsie, pilnowa ich, aby np. Nie mielimy dostpu
the orders route if we're not authenticated.
do trasy zamwie, jeli nie bdziemy uwierzytelnieni.
And additionally, I also want to pass that token we'll receive onto the backend for requests to protect
I dodatkowo chc przekaza ten token, ktry otrzymamy na zapleczu, za proby o ochron
resources so that we can make sure that this does not work.
zasobw, abymy mogli upewni si, e to nie zadziaa.
These are the adjustments we have to make on our frontend and to make them,
S to poprawki, ktre musimy wprowadzi na naszym interfejsie i aby je
we first of all will start with the sign up and sign in view because without having users, all the
wprowadzi, najpierw zaczniemy od rejestracji i logowania, poniewa bez posiadania uytkownikw wszystkie
other things are kind of hard to do.
inne rzeczy s trudne do zrobienia.